Minos.
Minos.
What are you doing?
- Qu'est-ce que tu fais ? - Yurine.
I'm grilling lobsters.
Je cuis les homards.
I think those are crawfi--
Ce sont des écre...
When I told Jashin-chan
Quand j'ai dit à Jashin-chan
I wanted to try lobster...
que je voulais du homard...
Big catch at Shimizu Canal around the corner!
Belle prise au Canal Shimizu à côté !
And then she gave me all this!
Elle m'a donné tout ça !
A BUNCH
BEAUCOUP
-Want some? -No.
- Tu en veux ? - Non.
-I'll grill some. -No, thanks.
- Je les grille.
Looking good!
Ça semble exquis !
Let's try it. Ouch! It's hot.
Goûtons. Aïe ! C'est chaud.
There. Let's eat!
Voilà. Mangeons !
Amazing! Nothing beats lobster!
Incroyable ! Il n'y a rien comme le homard !
100% BEEF
100 % BŒUF
-Crawfish is good? -Try some, Yurine!
- C'est bon, l'écrevisse ? - Goûte !
-No, thanks. -It's so crunchy.
- Merci. - C'est croustillant.
Pretty darn good!
C'est trop bon !
Won’t leave
Je ne partirai pas
without a dropkick on her!
Sans lui avoir balancé un dropkick !
Zazas Zazas Nasatanada Zazas
Zazas Zazas Nasatanada Zazas
-She summoned me, the evil god. -Evil god!
- Elle m'a appelée, moi, la démone. - Démone
-I gotta kill her or else -What?
- Je vais la tuer sinon - Quoi ?
-I can’t go back to Hell! -Sister...
- Je ne pourrai pas regagner l'enfer - Sœur
Yeah! Yeah! Yeah! Life next to death, I combat with my chainsaw!
La vie côtoie la mort Je lutte avec ma tronçonneuse
If you go too far,
Si tu vas trop loin
I’ll slice you up completely!
Je te taillerai en pièces
Your halo! Must get it back!
Ton auréole Tu dois la récupérer
-Never miss a chance -Hey, seriously?
- Tu ne rates pas une occasion - Sérieux ?
-To attack her from behind! -You’re so mean.
- L'attaquer par derrière - Tu es méchante
I’ll never give up.
Je ne lâcherai jamais.
Yurine, you’re off your guard!
Yurine, tu es sans défense
Now! Time to finish you with the Royal Copenhagen!
Maintenant Finissons-en avec le Royal Copenhagen
Huh? What? I missed…
Quoi ? J'ai raté...
Can’t leave Earth
Je ne peux pas quitter la Terre
without a dropkick on her!
Sans lui avoir balancé un dropkick
But until then,
Mais en attendant
-let’s all have fun together! -Yeah!
- On va bien s'amuser - Oui
What about my present?
Et mon cadeau ?
Of course I'll buy you one.
Je t'en achèterai un, bien sûr.
Really? Thanks!
Vraiment ? Merci !
That's right.
C'est vrai.
It's Christmas.
C'est Noël.
I'm so hungry.
J'ai si faim.
And I'm having bread crust.
Et je mange une croûte de pain.
My Lord endured hardships too.
Mon Seigneur a enduré, lui aussi.
I should be grateful for the food I have!
Je devrais être reconnaissante.
-It's cold. -So, what do you want for Christmas?
- Il fait froid. - Que veux-tu pour Noël ?
I want wealth, honor and status.
La richesse, l'honneur et un statut.
That's pretty mature of you.
Quelle maturité.
I'm sure Santa will make it happen.
Je suis sûr que le Père Noël t'entendra.
Then, I want love.
Dans ce cas, je veux de l'amour.
-Whoa, that's so cool. -Right?
- C'est trop cool. - Oui.
I want love.
Je veux de l'amour.
So cool.
Trop cool.
Santa? Must be talking about Saint Nicholas.
Le Père Noël ? Il s'agit sans doute de Saint Nicolas.
He's got a lot on his plate.
Sa tâche est lourde.
How will he fulfill these kids' wishes?
Comment combler les désirs de tous ces enfants ?
I wish for something with bold flavor.
Je voudrais quelque chose de savoureux.
Why am I wishing for a Christmas present
Pourquoi souhaiter un cadeau de Noël
when I'm not even human!?
si je ne suis pas humaine ?
To begin with, Christmas isn't even about presents!
Pour commencer, Noël, ce n'est pas que les cadeaux.
Shoot, I'm choking! I need something to drink!
Zut, je m'étouffe ! Il faut boire quelque chose !
MILK
LAIT
That was close.
C'était moins une.
I almost drank it all.
J'ai presque tout bu.
This is all I have for today.
Je n'ai que ça pour la journée.
I'm grateful for the food I have.
J'apprécie cette nourriture.
But I'm craving something with more flavor. Like curry.
Mais j'ai si envie d'un plat savoureux. Comme un curry.
Santa, will you visit an angel?
Père Noël, viendras-tu visiter un ange ?
Delicious.
C'est délicieux.
This smell...
Ce parfum...
So good.
C'est si bon.
-Curry? -This curry is amazing.
- Un curry ? - Il est délicieux.
Yurine Hanazono's familiar spirit. Why is she here?
L'esprit de Yurine Hanazono. Que fait-elle ici ?
Wait, that hat.
Attends, ce bonnet.
-Is she Saint Nicholas' spirit? -I got the take-out deal.
- L'esprit de Saint Nicolas ? - J'ai pris pour emporter.
-So good! -Was she sent for me?
- C'est bon ! - C'est pour moi ?
-It was so good, I devoured it all. -Nope.
- C'était bon. J'ai tout mangé. - Non.
I'll eat the second one too.
Je vais manger le deuxième.
It smells wonderful!
Quel parfum extraordinaire !
Curry...
Curry...
So juicy!
Si juteux !
Juicy...
Juteux...
What are you staring at?
Qu'est-ce que tu regardes ?
-None for you. -I couldn't help it.
- Ce n'est pas pour toi. - C'est plus fort que moi.
How embarrassing.
C'est gênant.
-I want that. -Huh?
Je veux ça.
Give it to me.
Donne.
You just had a feast.
Tu viens d'avaler un festin.
This is all I have.
C'est tout ce que j'ai.
I finished my food, so give me that.
J'ai tout mangé, alors donne.
You glutton. You'll end up in Hell.
Gloutonne. Tu finiras en enfer.
Funny. I'm from there.
Très drôle. Je viens de là.
I don't care. I'm still hungry!
Je m'en fiche. J'ai encore faim !
-Stop! This is all I have! -Shut up! Give it to me!
- Arrête ! Je n'ai que ça. - Tais-toi ! Donne !
M-My precious milk!
Mon lait précieux !
Your back's wide open!
Tu as le dos découvert !
Merry Christmas!
Joyeux Noël !
-Thanks. -No!
- Merci. - Non !
Delicious! Stolen food is out-of-this-world good.
Délicieux ! Il n'y a pas mieux que de la nourriture volée.
It's a bit dry, but delicious nonetheless.
C'est un peu sec, mais néanmoins délicieux.
H-How cruel.
Quelle cruauté.
You're the one who turned your back on me.
C'est toi qui m'as tourné le dos.
And thanks for the compliment.
Merci pour le compliment.
Give me back my precious food!
Rends-moi ma nourriture précieuse.
I'm not scared of you, halo-less angel!
Tu ne me fais pas peur, ange sans auréole !
What the hell are you doing?
Qu'est-ce que tu fais ?
Ah! Yurine...
Yurine !
I told you to go home with the curry while I got the chicken.
Tu devais ramener le curry tandis que je m'occupe du poulet.
The witch, Yurine Hanazono.
La sorcière, Yurine Hanazono.
-I don't know. -Huh? What?
- Je ne sais pas. - Quoi ?
I don't know.
Je ne sais pas.
You ate the curry?
Tu as mangé le curry ?
-Both of them? -I don't know anything.
- Toutes les deux ? - Je ne sais rien.
Where am I? Who am I?
Où suis-je ? Qui suis-je ?
I don't know.
Je ne sais pas.
-She ate it! -What?
- Elle l'a mangé ! - Quoi ?
She's tiny, but she can eat.
Elle est petite, mais elle mange.
-I told her no, but... -Jashin-chan.
- Je ne voulais pas, mais... - Jashin-chan.
Why lie about it?
Pourquoi mens-tu ?
Fine, I ate it!
D'accord, je l'ai mangé !
So?
Alors ?
Unbelievable.
Incroyable.
-As punishment, no chicken for you. -Oh come on...
- Pas de poulet pour toi. - Allons...
T-Takoyaki... Blood...
Takoyaki... Du sang...
-T-Takoyaki... -Pekola.
- Takoyaki... - Pekola.
Jashin-chan gave you a lot of trouble.
Jashin-chan t'a embêtée.
Please accept my apologies.
Accepte mes excuses.
This is Jashin-chan's chicken.
Le poulet de Jashin-chan.
Food with bold flavor!
Un plat savoureux.
I-I can't accept anything from a witch.
Je ne peux rien accepter d'une sorcière.
No way!
Je ne peux pas !
I'm still an angel, you know?
Je suis un ange, tu sais ?
You could've poisoned it too.
Tu as pu l'empoisonner.
This is an apology, accept it.
C'est une réparation. Accepte.
To eat it or not is your choice.
Tu décideras si tu le manges ou pas.
Jashin-chan, we're going home.
Jashin-chan, on rentre.
It's time to decorate our place. Wanna be the tree?
Il faut décorer la maison. Tu veux faire l'arbre ?
Chicken! With bold flavors.
Du poulet ! Savoureux.
Yurine Hanazono.
Yurine Hanazono.
-You're a witch, but my Santa! -Why don't I gift your meat to Beth?
- Tu es une sorcière et mon Père Noël. - Et si je donnais ta viande à Beth ?
Please don't...
S'il te plaît, non.
You like it, huh? Eat as much as you want.
Ça te plaît ? Mange autant que tu veux.
Jashin-chan, do you know?
Jashin-chan, tu sais ?
Why Santa's outfit is red?
Pourquoi l'habit du Père Noël est-il rouge ?
It's because it's stained in blood.
Parce qu'il est taché de sang.
Merry Christmas.
Joyeux Noël.
Merry Christmas-sacre! Huh?
Joyeux Noël-sacre !
Jashin-chan, where are you?
Jashin-chan, où es-tu ?
Jashin-chan... Jashin-chan...
Jashin-chan...
-Will she ever find her?
Saura-t-elle la retrouver ?
I'm right here, getting crucified.
Je suis là, crucifiée.
The seasons change in a blink of an eye.
Les saisons changent en un clin d'œil.
It's now deep autumn.
Voilà déjà l'automne.
Done with training.
Fini l'entraînement.
My own breathing method is doing me great.
Ma respiration fait des miracles.
These abs will make my dropkick more lethal.
Avec ces abdos, mon dropkick sera plus mortel.
Yurine, punch me in the stomach.
Yurine, frappe-moi au ventre.
Test out these abs of steel.
On va tester ces abdos d'acier.
All right.
D'accord.
Damn it.
Zut.
Jashin-chan?
Jashin-chan ?
Coming!
J'arrive !
Hello, my name is Yusa.
Bonjour, je m'appelle Yusa.
Thank you for taking care of my sister.
Merci de vous occuper de ma sœur.
Yusa? Um...
Yusa...
Enjoy.
Bon appétit.
Thank you.
Merci.
I planned on eating this cake all by myself!
J'avais prévu manger tout le gâteau !
REGAINED CONSCIOUSNESS
A REPRIS CONSCIENCE
Should've had it before my training!
J'aurais dû le manger avant l'entraînement.
Kori-chan saved us during the summer.
Kori-chan nous a sauvées l'été dernier.
But could you please stop the blizzard? It's freezing.
Tu peux arrêter le blizzard ? On gèle.
Oh, of course.
Bien sûr.
I know you two are sisters,
Je sais que vous êtes sœurs,
but are you even the same organism?
mais êtes-vous du même organisme ?
Yes.
Oui.
We, Ice Devils, change appearances as we grow.
Nous, Démones de Glace, changeons d'apparence en grandissant.
We're born with certain abilities as a child.
Nous naissons avec certaines aptitudes.
But when we mature, like I did,
Mais en grandissant comme j'ai grandi,
we receive a name and become a full-fledged devil.
nous recevons un nom et devenons une véritable démone.
In human years, Ice Devils mature at around 15 years old.
En années humaines, nous atteignons la maturité vers 15 ans.
I see.
Je vois.
May I suggest Kori-chan's future name?
Puis suggérer un nom pour Kori-chan ?
How about Koji?
Que dirais-tu de Koji ?
YUSA KOJI
YUSA KOJI
Isn't that a boy's name?
C'est un nom de garçon ?
I guess so.
Je crois.
Koji?
Koji ?
So, what brings you here today?
Qu'est-ce qui t'amène aujourd'hui ?
Yes, we didn't mean to show up unannounced,
On ne voulait pas venir à l'improviste,
but my sister begged me to take her to see you.
mais ma sœur m'a suppliée de l'emmener te voir.
We brought this for you.
Nous avons apporté ça pour toi.
-I heard she had fun with her. -Damn it! Such a thin slice.
- Elle s'est bien amusée avec elle. - Zut ! Trop fine, la tranche.
So, I wanted to thank her too.
Je voulais la remercier aussi.
Why the hell is she glaring at me like she wants to kill me?
Pourquoi ce regard assassin ?
Is she actually here to kill me?
Est-elle venue me tuer ?
Mature Ice Devils are high-class devils.
Une Démone de glace adulte est une démone supérieure.
She could kill me in a second!
Elle peut me tuer en une seconde !
DEFEATIST WHEN FACING STRONG DEVILS
DÉFAITISTE FACE AUX DÉMONES FORTES
Jashin-chan, did you do something?
Jashin-chan, tu as fait quelque chose ?
She whistled in your ear just to mess with you?
Elle a sifflé dans ton oreille pour t'embêter ?
-You're only 95 yen. -She stuck a bread-price tag on you?
- Seulement 95 yens. - Elle t'a collé une étiquette de pain ?
Koji! You snitch!
Koji ! Cafteuse !
You're such an idiot.
Tu es vraiment idiote.
Now she's traumatized with the sound of the whistle.
Elle est traumatisée avec ce sifflement.
And she can't even step inside a grocery store anymore.
Elle ne peut plus entrer au supermarché.
That's ridiculous!
C'est ridicule !
She's the low-class devil who disobeyed me!
C'est la démone minable qui m'a désobéi !
You insulted her again.
Tu l'as encore insultée.
When you insult her, you insult our proud family.
Quand tu l'insultes, tu insultes notre fière famille.
What proud family?
Quelle fière famille ?
You have the face of a mole.
Tu as une tête de taupe.
What's there to be proud of?
Il n'y a pas de quoi être fière.
A mole?
Une taupe ?
Did you just call her a mole?
Tu l'as traitée de taupe ?
I planned on leaving peacefully today.
Je prévoyais partir paisiblement aujourd'hui.
But now, you’ve said it.
Mais puisque tu l'as dit.
You said the last thing an Ice Devil wants to hear.
Tu as dit ce qu'aucune Démone de glace ne veut entendre.
What? Just go home, will ya?
Quoi ? Rentre chez toi !
It's freezing in here!
On gèle !
Koji's a piece of cake, but her? Forget about it.
Koji n'est pas compliquée. Mais elle ? C'est dingue.
What do I do? Think of something quick!
Que faire ? Réfléchis vite.
There must be an effective way...
Il doit y avoir moyen de...
Oh, yeah!
Oui !
What the hell is that?
Qu'est-ce que c'est ?
Idiot! It's nothing!
Idiote ! C'est rien !
You're done, Koji! Face your back at me like that!
Tu es fichue, Koji ! Tourne-moi le dos comme ça.
I'll pierce you with a dropkick now enhanced with my abs of steel!
Je vais te balancer un dropkick amélioré avec mes abdos d'acier.
Killing you in front of your sister will devastate her.
Te tuer devant ta sœur va l'anéantir.
She'll be too unstable to fight.
Elle sera trop instable pour se battre.
And best of all, I'll win!
Mieux, je gagnerai !
Let's not forget...!
N'oublions pas !
Jeez, not again.
C'est pas vrai.
My abs of steel were completely useless.
Mes abdos d'acier n'ont servi à rien.
Do you think you can let Jashin-chan go for today?
Peux-tu laisser Jashin-chan tranquille aujourd'hui ?
Sure. And I'm so glad my sister got to see you, Yurine.
Bien sûr. Je suis contente que ma sœur t'ait vue, Yurine.
I got the slice to stand upright! Hell, yeah!
J'ai réussi à la faire tenir debout ! Super !
It stands! It stands! It stands!
Elle tient !
HELL BANK JINBOCHO BRANCH
BANQUE DE L'ENFER SUCCURSALE JINBOCHO
Here, I brought the money.
Voilà, j'ai apporté de l'argent.
Can't you be discreet?
Sois plus discrète !
I don't want Yurine to know!
Yurine ne doit pas savoir.
S-Sorry.
Désolée.
Too late now.
Trop tard.
Sponging off Medusa again?
Tu éponges Medusa encore ?
N-Not at all.
Pas du tout.
She's just paying me back.
Elle me rembourse.
You're the lowest of the low.
Tu es vraiment minable.
She knows.
Elle sait.
I-I'm just borrowing it.
Je ne fais qu'emprunter.
I always pay her back.
Je rembourse toujours.
I paid her back the 40 yen I borrowed 100 years ago.
J'ai lui ai remboursé 40 yens empruntés il y a 100 ans.
That's the initial salary of 100 years ago.
C'est la somme initiale d'il y a 100 ans.
I don't really need her to pay me back.
Elle n'a pas besoin de me rembourser.
Right? It's best to assume the money you lend will never come back.
Il vaut mieux se dire que l'argent prêté est perdu à jamais.
You have no right to say that.
Tu n'as pas le droit de dire ça.
Medusa, you're spoiling her a bit too much.
Medusa, tu la gâtes trop.
You're enabling her to be a scumbag.
Tu lui permets d'être une fripouille.
A scumbag? No, that's not good!
Une fripouille ? Non, ce n'est pas bien.
Right? So, you have to be responsible with her.
Il faut se montrer responsable avec elle.
What, Medusa?
Quoi, Medusa ?
You're gonna listen to her?
Tu vas l'écouter ?
You've known me for thousands of years and yet, you choose Yurine?
Tu me connais depuis des milliers d'années, et tu choisis Yurine ?
You traitor!
Traîtresse !
Ah, here we go again.
C'est reparti.
I-It's not like that. I'm just concerned for you.
Ce n'est pas ça. Je suis juste inquiète pour toi.
Liar!
Menteuse !
You just like yourself acting like a goody two-shoes!
Tu te comportes comme une sainte nitouche !
I hate you, Jashin-chan!
Je te déteste, Jashin-chan !
I don't care about you anymore.
Tant pis pour toi.
I'm never coming back to the human world again!
Je ne reviendrai plus dans le monde des humains.
I don't need you! Don't ever come back!
Je n'ai pas besoin de toi ! Ne reviens jamais.
I said a bit too much.
J'ai trop parlé.
Medusa...
Medusa...
Medusa hates me now.
Medusa me déteste maintenant.
Medusa was, to me...
Pour moi, Medusa était...
She was my precious...
Elle était ma chère...
Precious...
Ma chère...
-Personal ATM. -I knew that was coming.
- Ma chère DAB. - Je l'attendais.
Say cheese!
Souriez !
I highly recommend the cheesy pizza toast. It's tasty!
Je recommande cette tartine au fromage. Si savoureuse.
Can't go on without a drink!
J'ai besoin de boire.
She said she's never coming back.
Elle a dit qu'elle ne reviendrait jamais.
Now I gotta make her send the money via Hell-registered mail.
Elle devra m'envoyer l'argent par courrier recommandé-enfer.
I don't need to see her face.
Pas besoin de voir sa tête.
Another fresh strawberry juice please!
Un autre jus de fraise, s'il vous plaît !
You're drinking too much.
Vous buvez trop.
Leave me alone.
Laissez-moi tranquille.
Having too much strawberry juice won't kill me.
Ça ne me tuera pas de boire trop de jus de fraise.
I'm not concerned about you.
Ce n'est pas pour vous.
We don't want to run out for the other customers.
Mais à ce rythme, il en manquera pour les autres.
Oh.
Ah bon.
I can't even get myself to walk.
Je n'arrive plus à marcher.
This is so sad!
C'est trop triste.
Medusa left me.
Medusa m'a quittée.
And nobody cares about me!
Je n'intéresse personne !
I...
Je...
Did I do something that bad? Maybe I did, but still!
J'ai fait quelque chose de mal ? Peut-être, mais quand même.
Come on, can't you just love me for who I am?
Ne pouvez-vous pas m'aimer pour ce que je suis ?
Come on! Just love me, please!
Aimez-moi, s'il vous plaît !
-Love me for who I am! -What's wrong with you?
- Aimez-moi pour ce que je suis. - Ça va pas ?
What's wrong with me?
Qu'est-ce qui ne va pas chez moi ?
Take me away.
Emmenez-moi.
I'm lonely!
Je me sens seule.
Calm down, will ya?
Calmez-vous.
Jashin-chan?
Jashin-chan ?
I'm hearing voices now.
J'entends des voix.
I've lost my mind.
J'ai perdu la tête.
Jashin-chan.
Jashin-chan.
Medusa's voice.
La voix de Medusa.
I didn't lose my mind.
Je n'ai pas perdu la tête.
I came to pick you up.
Je suis venue te chercher.
Y-You came back to me, my ATM!
Tu es revenue, ma DAB ?
Medusa was so worried, she came right back.
Medusa était si inquiète qu'elle est revenue.
A... T...
D... A...
It was all my fault Forgive me, AT--
C'est ma faute. Pardonne-moi, DA...
No, Medusa!
Non, Medusa !
I know, Jashin-chan.
Je sais, Jashin-chan.
You can't function without me.
Tu ne peux pas vivre sans moi.
I love you, Medusa.
Je t'aime, Medusa.
At... the... moment...
Doux ange béni.
I love you at the moment, Medusa!
Je t'aime, doux ange béni !
At the moment!
Doux ange béni !
ATM!
DAB !
Jashin-chan, aren't you hungry?
Jashin-chan, tu as faim ?
Let's get some curry.
Allons chercher un curry.
What happened?
Que s'est-il passé ?
I'm completely broke because I had 100 glasses of strawberry juice.
Je n'ai pas d'argent car j'ai bu cent verres de jus de fraise.
Don't worry, I'll take care of the bill.
Ne t'inquiète pas, je réglerai.
I just can't live without you, Medusa.
Je ne peux pas vivre sans toi.
I love you, Medusa!
Je t'aime, Medusa !
I'll never leave you again, Jashin-chan.
Je ne te quitterai plus jamais, Jashin-chan.
-Medusa just enabled her to become -Where should we go?
- A cause de Medusa, elle sera - On va où ?
-the ultra-scumbag. -Bondy, of course!
- la pire des fripouilles. - Chez Bondy.
-Let's go! -Yay!
- Allons-y ! - Oui !
SCUMBAG
SALAUD
-Medusa. -Jashin-chan.
- Medusa. - Jashin-chan.
Dropkick on her! Yeah her! I’ll take you down again!
Dropkick pour elle, oui elle Je finirai par t'avoir
Hate you! Love doesn’t exist in this world
Je te déteste L'amour n'existe pas dans ce monde
Fear the dropkick! An Angel looks for her halo
Crains le dropkick Un ange cherche son auréole
As she starves to death!
Alors qu'elle meure de faim
It’s a love and hate relationship,
C'est une relation d'amour et de haine
can’t leave each other alone
Elles ne peuvent pas se quitter
Like a galaxy-bursting shooting star!
Comme une étoile filante Qui traverse la galaxie
Slowly, slowly, sneak up and DIE!
Lentement, lentement Approche-toi et MEURS !
Test my heart, don’t stop
Eprouve mon cœur, n'arrête pas
Let’s go! Dream on! No matter human, angel or devil
Allez, rêve Humain, ange ou démone
We’re a happy family La la la
Nous sommes une famille heureuse
Let me say, I love you!!
Sache que je t'aime
When all is said and done
Quand tout sera fini
I’m home! Welcome back, it’s hot pot tonight!
Je suis rentrée Bienvenue, il y a du ragoût ce soir
Come, gather everyone! Let’s enjoy this meal!
Réunissons-nous Profitons de ce repas
For another crazy tomorrow
Pour un lendemain fou
What next? What next? In the end, Wakeup!
Quoi ensuite ? Finalement, réveille-toi
There's a lady enticing the devil.
Une femme attire la démone.
Love and hate are two sides of the same coin.
Amour et haine, deux côtés d'une même médaille.
So with her pure love, she tries to kill the devil.
Avec son amour pur, elle essaie de tuer la démone.
Dropkick on My Devil! We'll backdrop your heart in the next episode too!
Dropkick on My Devil ! Cœur secoué au prochain épisode.